<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</title>
    <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Classic VW Restorations</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/classicvws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/classicvws/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview This Project was created for a local auto shop specializing in Classic Volkswagons out of Fullerton CA. Classicvws.shop is built on WordPress using the popular site builder plugin Elementor Pro, and is hosted on an AWS EC2 Instance using the Bitnami Wordpress AMI.
Development  Created a custom post type for projects as a plugin using a GenerateWP template. Activated Elementor license and updated stock templates for archive lists and single pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean O&#39;Brien Paintings &amp; Illustrations</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/smozart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/smozart/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview This Project showcases sample artwork for a sole proprietor interested in selling their custom-commissioned art services online. Sean&amp;rsquo;s a friend of mine and he was interested in starting a new business painting pets and family portraits. What we agreed to build for him was an ecommerce solution built entirely on the JAMstack concept using Hugo SSG as a storefront, Vue.js as a checkout application, and a few APIs to manage the cart, payments, and file uploading functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stoubord&#39;s Picks: Video RSS Directory</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/stoubord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/stoubord/</guid>
      <description>Overview Stoubord&amp;rsquo;s picks is my first attempt to aggregate video content from YouTube creators by RSS feeds. The plan was to build this project on wordpress and then use the BuddyPress plugin to create a user-community. Users would update a directory of creators as well as niche tags on creator profiles to help the community find similar content.
Core Functions The whole project revolves our Feeds class found within our child theme&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
