<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</title>
    <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Retrospective: Art Shop eCommerce on JAMstack</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/artretro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/artretro/</guid>
      <description>This has been by far my favorite project to work on in regards to using a technology stack, specifically the JAMStack. It was my first time building an application this way, but it&amp;rsquo;s rewarding on multiple levels: I&amp;rsquo;ve helped a friend succeed as an entreprenuer, built a product almost any business can start with, and saw valuable opportunities to extend on it.
This site in particular uses two hosted github page repos based on code published by CommerceLayer for use with their API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) and Crypto&#39;s Future For the Music Industry</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/nft-music-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/nft-music-future/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest critiques I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered from bearish investors like Peter Schiff regarding Bitcoin and Cryptocurrencies as a whole is that it&amp;rsquo;s intangible. The internet itself is intangible in the same sense, yet everyone uses it without thinking of the hardware, network layers, and other protocols that facilitate everything we do online. No one calls it a fad anymore, but they used to as well. Blockchain technology will progress in a similar fashion, and Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) are a new value proposition that ties the tech to a swath of new real-world use cases, and music industry is only one facet of this upcoming economic boom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
