<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Stouffer on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</title>
    <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/authors/alex-stouffer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alex Stouffer on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexstouffer.github.io/authors/alex-stouffer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Classic VW Restorations</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/classicvws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/classicvws/</guid>
      <description>This project is currently being launched on AWS and will be updated shortly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memepact: Video RSS Service</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/memepact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/memepact/</guid>
      <description>Turns out this project was shut down while minimizing projects to save some CA$H. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to update this page once I have everything set up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Marketplace Slays Competition When It Comes To Getting The Best Price For Your Gear</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/reverb-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 17:20:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/reverb-guide/</guid>
      <description>It might have been that back in the day, eBay was the best place to reach a wide market of interested customers. Over time though, eBays reputation has diminished with sellers due to burdensome requirements. Online reviews from sellers claim that they are required to accept returns and refund the money even when the returned item is damaged when shipped back. While that&amp;rsquo;s worth verifying from eBays Terms and Conditions specifically, that should be a major red flag for anyone invested in shipping inventory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) and Crypto&#39;s Future For the Music Industry</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/nft-music-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/nft-music-future/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest critiques I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered from bearish investors like Peter Schiff regarding Bitcoin and Cryptocurrencies as a whole is that it&amp;rsquo;s intangible. The internet itself is intangible in the same sense, yet everyone uses it without thinking of the hardware, network layers, and other protocols that facilitate everything we do online. No one calls it a fad anymore, but they used to as well. Blockchain technology will progress in a similar fashion, and Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) are a new value proposition that ties the tech to a swath of new real-world use cases, and music industry is only one facet of this upcoming economic boom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Roadmap To Selling Student-Tailored Video Courses</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:36:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Private music teachers found themselves in an interesting situation last year during COVID-19 Pandemic shutdowns. They found that their jobs as they knew them had been destabilized as long they required that the money needed to be made from teaching students in person at a physical location. Many adapted quickly and began teaching courses through Zoom, Skype, and other video conferencing apps that allowed two musicians to play for eachother from remote locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Round Here: In Memorium of Mike &#39;Deezy&#39; DeBord</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/multimedia/deezy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/multimedia/deezy/</guid>
      <description>This is a memorial video for my Stepdad Mike DeBord who passed away following an ultimately fatal motorcycle accident, while riding in Angeles National Forrest, in July of 2017. It showcases VHS Cassettes of family home videos from his side of the family with footage superimposed from the old man&amp;rsquo;s own Instagram account. Photos are keyframed to give them motion similar to the technique Ken Burns uses for photos in his documentaries, and the pace of editing was set to my Dad&amp;rsquo;s own personal anthem: Around Here by Counting Crows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Do&#39;s and Dont&#39;s of Cleaning Guitars</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/cleaning-dos-donts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/cleaning-dos-donts/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember that episode of The Wonder Years where Kevin Arnold&amp;rsquo;s Dad was finally convinced to sell the old family station wagon? The family loved the allure of trading up to a newer vehicle, but once they began to wash that wagon one last time nostalgia feels slapped at their heartstrings. It&amp;rsquo;s kind of like that the first time you sell your old guitar. You remember your first riffs. Your first band.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
