<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Stouffer on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</title>
    <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/authors/alex-stouffer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alex Stouffer on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 19:14:07 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexstouffer.github.io/authors/alex-stouffer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Host Images on an AWS S3 Bucket</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/image-hosting-on-aws-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/image-hosting-on-aws-s3/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Web Service&amp;rsquo;s S3 Buckets are my preferred method for inserting images into content that might go into things like email signatures. While a free service like Dropbox could be used instead, images don&amp;rsquo;t always reliably show when composing new emails. That can leave people within an organization confused about whether their signatures will appear correctly on the receiving end, and they may spend unnecessary time asking IT departments whether their signatures are working as intended or testing it themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Email Signatures Across Different Operating Systems and Clients</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/image-hosting-on-aws-s3-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/image-hosting-on-aws-s3-copy/</guid>
      <description>The time has come, and we&amp;rsquo;re at the final step: installing your new professional email signature! Depending on which desktop operating system you&amp;rsquo;re using, you may have to follow different steps to get your new HTML email signature to appear consistently. Here&amp;rsquo;s a couple links on installing for Windows and Mac versions of Outlook respectively:
 How to install on Windows How to install on Mac  For information on installing to Gmail, please view this video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win Clients With Professional Email Signatures</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/custom-email-signature-templating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/custom-email-signature-templating/</guid>
      <description>We always want to approach our sales prospects with the utmost professionalism whether we&amp;rsquo;re working independently or as part of a larger organization. That can be pretty challenging when the best option to present ourself is a cold email. They don&amp;rsquo;t know who we are or our reputation. If a client can&amp;rsquo;t gauge that quickly they will not burn their valuable time to consider our proposition. However, there are many things we can do to improve our chances with new clients over cold emails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Custom Post Types From WordPress to Next.js using GraphQL and Vercel Hosting</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/migrate-cpt-from-wordpress-to-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/migrate-cpt-from-wordpress-to-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>I built an RSS reader that pulls content from my favorite YouTube creators, and gives it to me without any kind of algorithmic influence. It’s a current portfolio project built with WordPress that relies on ‘the core’ of conventional WordPress CMS development. While I’m proud of the work I did using Advanced Customer Fields and writing PHP scripts, the site still doesn’t have a very nice User Interface/Experience to present the data that’s being served.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Integrate WordPress with Next.js</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/leverage-wordpress-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/leverage-wordpress-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>WordPress Sites account for ~40% of all websites and ~60% of all sites that use a Content Management System. Despite the overwhelming adoption, WordPress has some significant disadvantages that could be overcome with Next.js:
Slow page speeds &amp;amp; Poor SEO ranking Wordpress can be excellent when optimized by a skilled developer, and maybe that&amp;rsquo;s your case. However for every 1 site that&amp;rsquo;s optimized there are at least a dozen that aren&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Sales Tracker</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/niftybot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/niftybot/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview I built a Nifty Bot that tracks sales for a single collection of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs). For showcasing purposes I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to spin up a bot for a new collection in the space that I love called &amp;ldquo;GEMMA&amp;rdquo; by Los Angeles based artist Tristan Eaton. This collection is a series of 5k portraits all generated programatically under the artist&amp;rsquo;s direction. I feel it&amp;rsquo;s a great representation of what this new area of art has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean&#39;s Custom Art Shop</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/obrienart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/obrienart/</guid>
      <description>Many people dream of owning their own business but they are limited to a small yet engaged audience on social media. If that sounds like a problem you are dealing with this Art Shop is the solution. You can finally own your own business from home and without too much investment capital. This package features an automated sales pipeline and grouped products or services. It met the original stakeholder&amp;rsquo;s 3 main requirements: a blog to promote work, a shop to sell directly from home, and no monthly fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Retrospective: Art Shop eCommerce on JAMstack</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/artretro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/artretro/</guid>
      <description>This has been my favorite project to work on. Using the JAMStack made it particularly enjoyable. It was my first time building an application this way, but it is rewarding on multiple levels: I&amp;rsquo;ve helped an artist succeed as an entrepreneur, built a product almost any business can start with, and saw valuable opportunities to extend on it.
This site uses two hosted GitHub page repos based on code published by CommerceLayer for use with their API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stoubord&#39;s Picks: Video RSS Directory</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/stoubord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/product/stoubord/</guid>
      <description>Overview Stoubord&amp;rsquo;s picks is my first attempt to aggregate video content from YouTube creators by RSS feeds. The plan was to build this project on wordpress and then use the BuddyPress plugin to create a user-community. Users would update a directory of creators as well as niche tags on creator profiles to help the community find similar content.
Core Functions The whole project revolves our Feeds class found within our child theme&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
