<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Stouffer-DeBord</title>
    <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alex Stouffer-DeBord</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexstouffer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sean&#39;s Custom Art Shop</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/obrienart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/obrienart/</guid>
      <description>Many people dream of owning their own business but they are limited to a small yet engaged audience on social media. If that sounds like a problem you are dealing with, this Art Shop Solution finally allows you to own your own business from home and without too much investment capital. This package features an automated sales pipeline and grouped products or services. It met the original stakeholder&amp;rsquo;s 3 main requirements: a blog to promote work, a shop to sell directly from home, and no monthly fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Retrospective: Art Shop eCommerce on JAMstack</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/artretro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/artretro/</guid>
      <description>This has been by far my favorite project to work on in regards to using a technology stack, specifically the JAMStack. It was my first time building an application this way, but it&amp;rsquo;s rewarding on multiple levels: I&amp;rsquo;ve helped a friend succeed as an entreprenuer, built a product almost any business can start with, and saw valuable opportunities to extend on it.
This site in particular uses two hosted github page repos based on code published by CommerceLayer for use with their API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic VW Restorations</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/classicvws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/classicvws/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview This Project was created for a local auto shop specializing in Classic Volkswagons out of Fullerton CA. Classicvws.shop is built on WordPress using the popular site builder plugin Elementor Pro, and is hosted on an AWS EC2 Instance using the Bitnami Wordpress AMI.
Development  Created a custom post type for projects as a plugin using a GenerateWP template. Activated Elementor license and updated stock templates for archive lists and single pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stoubord&#39;s Picks: Video RSS Directory</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/stoubord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/project/stoubord/</guid>
      <description>Overview Stoubord&amp;rsquo;s picks is my first attempt to aggregate video content from YouTube creators by RSS feeds. The plan was to build this project on wordpress and then use the BuddyPress plugin to create a user-community. Users would update a directory of creators as well as niche tags on creator profiles to help the community find similar content.
Core Functions The whole project revolves our Feeds class found within our child theme&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) and Crypto&#39;s Future For the Music Industry</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/nft-music-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/post/nft-music-future/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest critiques I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered from bearish investors like Peter Schiff regarding Bitcoin and Cryptocurrencies as a whole is that it&amp;rsquo;s intangible. The internet itself is intangible in the same sense, yet everyone uses it without thinking of the hardware, network layers, and other protocols that facilitate everything we do online. No one calls it a fad anymore, but they used to as well. Blockchain technology will progress in a similar fashion, and Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) are a new value proposition that ties the tech to a swath of new real-world use cases, and music industry is only one facet of this upcoming economic boom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Round Here: In Memorium of Mike &#39;Deezy&#39; DeBord</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/multimedia/deezy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/multimedia/deezy/</guid>
      <description>This is a memorial video for my Stepdad Mike DeBord who passed away following an ultimately fatal motorcycle accident, while riding in Angeles National Forrest, in July of 2017. It showcases VHS Cassettes of family home videos from his side of the family with footage superimposed from the old man&amp;rsquo;s own Instagram account. Photos are keyframed to give them motion similar to the technique Ken Burns uses for photos in his documentaries, and the pace of editing was set to my Dad&amp;rsquo;s own personal anthem: Around Here by Counting Crows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alexstouffer.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexstouffer.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Alex Stouffer and I&amp;rsquo;m a web developer invested in the future of decentralized internet. My goal in 2021 is to begin working on blockchain projects both personal and professional. I love playing music and reading to my infant daughter Lucia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
